Senan Memmedov FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Imemmedovsenan@gmail.com
 → +994 50 783 29 95
 ⊗ senan-portfolio.com
 ⊚ gsenan747
 ⊚ @1senanmemmedov
 im @senan-memmedov

I love creating web-sites. I have different types of projects. Everyday I try to develop my skills. My love for Front-end has grown because it provides me with the opportunity to shape and design my creative ideas. Improving user experiences and creating simple, intuitive interfaces are among my primary goals

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer (intern) | Vabiss

01/2024 - Present

Front-end developer (intern) | Techtonas company

10/2023 - 12/2023

- Creating a dashboard for logistics company.
- Worked with Next.js, React, MUI, Redux TK, RTK Query, Rest Api.

Front-end developer (volunteer) | Enactus club

04/2023 - Present

- Creating a dashboard and ecommerce website.
- Worked with Angular, Tailwind Css, Node.js.

EDUCATION

Information technologies | Academy of State Customs Committee

2021- Present

University projects

- Web version of firewall application(Login, Register, Firewall on-off, IP blocking, sending ping,) (Flask, JavaScript)
- ASCCA voting application (Dasboard, Voting page) (React, Node.js, MUI, Tailwind Css)

Marks: 88

SKILLS

• HTML • React is (core) (tsx, jsx)

RTK Query

• CSS (SCSS)

Next.is

• Redux TK

JavaScript

• Vue.js (understanding framework logic)

• Git

TypeScript

Material UI

• Figma

RESTful API

• Tailwind CSS - Bootstrap

• C++ (DSA, OOP)

• iQuery

• Node.js (limited backend experience)

LANGUAGES

- Azerbaijani (Native)
- English (B2)
- Turkish (Native)